Okay, if no one else will say it, I will.
(Raj:)We really suck at paintball.
HOWARD:
That was absolutely humiliating.
LEONARD: Oh, come on. Some battles
you win, some battles you lose.
HOWARD: Yes, but you don't have to lose
to Kyle Bernstein's bar mitzvah party.
(Leonard:)I think we have to acknowledge, those were
some fairly savage preadolescent Jews.
No, we were annihilated
by our own incompetence...
(Sheldon:)...and the inability of some people
to follow the chain of command.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, let it go.
No, I wanna talk about the fact
that Wolowitz shot me in the back.
I shot you for a good reason.
You were leading us into disaster.
(Sheldon:)I was giving clear, concise orders.
You hid behind a tree yelling:
"Get the kid in the yarmulke!
Get the kid in the yarmulke!"
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Oh, hey, Penny.
(Leonard:)- Hello.
- Morning, ma'am.